firebase security when you build a firebase app you can perform user
firebase 安全性 当您构建firebase 应用程序时，您可以完全从前端代码执行用户
authentication and work with your database entirely
身份验证并使用您的数据库
from your front-end code but how is this possible if our database
，但是如果我们的
is exposed on the client wouldn't that mean that any hacker could then read or
数据库暴露在客户端上，这怎么可能，这并不意味着任何黑客都可以读取或
write private user data the answer is no because your
编写私人用户数据 答案是否定的，因为您的
infrastructure is protected by a mechanism known as firebase security
基础架构受到称为 firebase 安全规则的机制的保护，
rules which can be applied to real-time database
该机制可应用于实时数据库
cloud storage and firestore in a traditional web application you have a
云存储和传统 Web 应用程序中的 firestore 您在该
server on that server you implement security
服务器上有一个服务器 您实现了安全
logic that uses either tokens or cookies to verify that a user making a request
逻辑 它使用令牌或 cookie来验证发出请求的用户是否
is authorized to do so firebase rules achieve the same thing but without the
被授权这样做，firebase 规则可以实现相同的目的，但
need to write maintain and deploy server-side code
无需编写维护和部署服务器端代码，
instead you create a policy to define who has access to what
而是创建一个策略来定义谁有权访问什么
in your database using a very easy to learn language called common expression
language whenever a user makes a request to read
每当用户请求读取
or write to your database that request is routed through this policy
或写入您的 d 数据库该请求通过此策略路由
every operation is denied by default when a request comes in
，默认情况下，每个操作都被拒绝当请求进入时
it will look for the first rule to allow it once allowed firebase can then
，它将寻找第一个规则以允许它一旦允许 firebase 然后可以
securely read or write to your database you can write rules from the firebase
安全地读取或写入您的数据库您可以从 firebase 控制台编写规则
console or your ide in the console you can time travel back to any previous
或 您在控制台中的 ide您可以时间旅行回到
rules you've used in the past or use the playground to send a mock request to
您过去使用过的任何以前的规则，或者使用操场向您的数据库发送模拟请求
your database and in production you can analyze
，在生产中您可以
exactly how your rules are being executed
准确分析您的规则是如何执行的
to enforce a rule we start by matching a path in the database
以强制执行规则 我们首先匹配数据库中的路径，该路径
which can be as broad as the entire database or as granular as a single
可以与整个数据库一样广泛，也可以与单个
document a single document can be matched with a
文档
collection followed by a document id if we want anybody to read and write to
一样细化
this document we can say allow read and write
我们可以说允许读写，
but that's not very secure let's make sure a user is logged into our app to
但这不是很安全让我们确保用户登录到我们的应用程序以
view the document which we can do by writing conditional
查看文档，我们可以通过编写
logic we allow the operation if the request auth object does not
允许操作的条件逻辑来完成如果在写入时请求身份验证对象不
equal null when it comes to writes we can make sure
等于 null，我们可以
only the user that owns the document can write to it by checking the request
确保只有拥有文档的用户才能通过检查请求
auth user id in most cases though you'll want your rules to apply to an entire
身份验证用户 ID 来写入它，尽管您希望您的规则适用于 整个
collection if we wrap the document id in braces the
集合如果我们将文档 ID 包装在大括号中，则
rule now applies to any document in that collection and we can use the document
规则现在适用于该集合中的任何文档，我们可以
id as a variable in our logic and now we
在逻辑中使用文档 ID 作为变量，现在我们
have a firebase app that's 100 secure without any vulnerabilities whatsoever
有一个 100 安全的 Firebase 应用程序，没有任何漏洞，
but there's a lot more to learn consider becoming a pro member at fireship io to
但是有 还有很多要学习的考虑成为 fireship io 的专业会员，
get access to the new firebase security master course where you'll learn all
以访问新的 firebase 安全大师课程，您将在其中学习
kinds of advanced techniques for real-world applications
各种用于实际应用的高级技术
thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
感谢观看，我们下期再见